the-numbers.com 2019-12-30

# 

**_The Numbers Privacy Policy_**

We at The Numbers are committed to protecting your online privacy. This statement is a description of the policy that governs how we collect and use information on The Numbers site. If you have any questions, please contact us at 8350 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 200, Beverly Hills, CA 90211.

Please note that if you leave [www.the-numbers.com](http://www.the-numbers.com/) (including if you click on any of the banner ads), you will be traveling outside of The Numbers and your information will be subject to privacy policy of the site to which you have traveled.  Please also note that we may change this privacy policy from time to time—you should check it regularly for changes—but we will never sell or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone else unless we are compelled to do so by law (see below). __

**_Information that we collect:_** ****

We collect only two kinds of information at The Numbers:  1) anonymous use information; and 2) information that you choose to give us through web forms when you register with The Numbers or choose to send e-mail to us. 

1)  When you browse The Numbers site, read or download information such as box office charts, movie reviews or the movie release chart, we collect only the following limited, anonymous data:

Our servers may record the numerical Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you 

are using, the operating system and browser you use, the date and time you access our 

The Numbers site, and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to The Numbers.

We use this information to diagnose system problems, to measure the number of visitors 

we receive and where what pages on The Numbers site are most popular (but we never conduct “audit trails” that measure what pages individual users visit), and to improve the site. We may also use this information to block computers that are attempting denial of service attacks on The Numbers servers or for similar security purposes. ****

We may share this anonymous information with selected affiliates of The Numbers, but we will never disclose information that identifies you personally to anyone outside of The Numbers unless compelled by law (see below).

2)  The Numbers also invites visitors to register via our online forms. You will need to register if you would like to participate in our forums, polls or contests, submit reviews or receive our monthly e-mail newsletter. 

The only information you must provide if you choose to register is your e-mail address. We use this information for verification purposes; also, if you sign up for our monthly newsletter (see below), then we will send the newsletter to the e-mail address you give us here. We will not disclose your e-mail address to anyone else unless compelled by law (see below). ****

You may choose to let use place a cookie on your PC if you would like to log on to The Numbers automatically. We will use the cookie only to log you on, and for no other purpose. ****

You may choose to give us basic anonymous demographic information (the city, state and country in which you live, your zip code, and your age group). We may use this information to provide you and other site users with analysis of the most popular movies in various age groups or areas, to provide movie listings in your zip code, etc. We may also share this general demographic information with selected affiliates of The Numbers, but again, we will never sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information about you unless we are compelled by law (see below). Providing us with this general demographic information is entirely optional—just leave the fields blank if you do not want to share it with us. 

If you would like to sign up for a contest or prize or to become a contributor to the site, we will need your mailing address.  We will use your mailing address to send you any prizes or necessary correspondence.  We will not sell or otherwise disclose your mailing address or password to anyone else unless we are compelled by law (see below). If you sign up for a contest or prize, however, we may use your name and your home state in a list of winners on the site. Please read the official rules for any contest.

You may also choose to receive our monthly newsletter, _The Number Crunch_ , by checking the relevant box when you register. You must voluntarily subscribe by checking the box in order to receive the newsletter.

You may also send e-mail to The Numbers via the e-mail address on The Numbers web site. When you choose do this, we collect the address of the e-mail account that you sent the message from and any information that you choose to include in the message.  We will not share this information with third parties unless compelled by law.

**_Information collected by third parties:_** ****

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit The Numbers. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**_Managing your information and “unsubscribing”:_**

If you want to get information about you that may be in our records, or if you want us to remove any correct any information you have given us via the online forms, just let us know. Contact the site administrator at: [remove@the-numbers.com](mailto:remove@the-numbers.com).

If you signed up to receive _The Number Crunch_ and you do not want to receive it __ anymore, just let us know by contacting us at [unsubscribe@the-numbers.com](mailto:unsubscribe@the-numbers.com) and we will remove you from the list.

**_Law enforcement and other compelled disclosures:_**

If we are required by law (including by a court order) to disclose any information you have submitted to us, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made and give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure.  We will attempt to give you this notice by e-mail, if you have given us an e-mail address, or by postal mail if you have given us a postal address.  If we are unable to contact you, if you do not challenge the disclosure request, or if we are still required to disclose the information despite your challenge, we will disclose it as required by law.

**_Security of information under our control:_**

Our databases, including the database of registered users and system administrations logs, are password protected. Password information is encrypted in the database. ** __**

A “cookie” is information that a web site puts on your hard disk so that it can remember something about you at a later time. Unless a web site uses a cookie, the web page server has no memory of what pages it has sent you previously or anything about your previous visits.
